Harvard University. Official register of Harvard University, 1900-2008: an inventory
Official register of Harvard University, 1900-2008
Harvard University Archives
HU 75.25
Harvard University.
52 cubic feet (163 document boxes)
The Official Register of Harvard University is a set of publications that has been published annually by Harvard since 1900. While specific titles included within the register have varied over time, much of the content has remained consistent, including annual reports of the president and treasurer, course catalogs, announcements of departments and divisions, student handbooks, and directories.
This document last updated 2012 September 6.
Scope Note
The Official Register of Harvard University is a set of publications that has been published annually by Harvard since 1900. While specific titles included within the register have varied over time, much of the content has remained consistent, including annual reports of the president and treasurer, course catalogs, announcements of departments and divisions, student handbooks, and directories.
The archivist has included information regarding missing or unpublished issues, when known, at the series level.
Since 2005, course catalog information has been available online.
Arrangement
Arranged in chronological order by year of publication. Within each year, arranged by volume and issue number.
Duplicate copies are arranged in chronological order at the end of the finding aid.
Related material
The Harvard University Archives holds additional copies of many of the titles represented in the Official Register. These copies are cataloged individually by title in HOLLIS, Harvard's on-line library catalog.
Annual reports
Report of the President of Harvard College: Harvard University Archives call number HU 30.10
Treasurer's statement: Harvard University Archives call number HU 35.10
Directories
Directory of University officers and students: Harvard University Archives call number HU 20.47
Catalogs
A-Cats provides access to Harvard's online course catalogs from Fall 2005 to the present.
Courses of instruction: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8500.16
General catalogue: Harvard University Archives call number HU 20.41
Harvard University catalogue: Harvard University Archives call number HU 20.41
Regulations and handbooks
Fields of concentration: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8500.28
Information concerning the departments under the charge of the Faculty of Arts and Sciences: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8500.40
Information for faculty offering instruction in arts and sciences: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 9541
Handbook for students, Harvard College: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 9536
Rules relating to college studies: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 9579
Information for special students in Harvard College: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8500.41
Studies in the freshman year: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8500.83
Advanced standing at Harvard College: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 517
Fellowships and scholarships administered by the Committee on General Scholarships and the Sheldon Fund: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 1000.11
Prizes open to students in Harvard College, Radcliffe College, the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, University Extension School and other Graduate Schools of the University: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 2000.5
Harvard College list of scholarships awarded: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 1000.xx
Admission to Harvard College: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 502
The houses: Harvard University Archives call number HUB 1456.20
Departmental and divisional announcements
Division of Ancient Languages: Department of the Classics and Department of Indic Philology: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8503.2
Department of Anthropology: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8503.7
Division of Applied Science: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8504.1
Department of Architecture: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8504.3
Department of architectural sciences: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8504.4
Asiatic studies at Harvard University: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8505.3
Department of astronomy: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8505.7
Concentration field in biochemical sciences: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8508.2
Department of Biology: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8508.7
Department of Chemistry: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8513.2
Department of the Classics and Department of Indic Philology: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8513.6
Department of Comparative Literature: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8514.4
Department of Comparative Philology: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8514.7
Division of Education: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8522.4
Department of Engineering Sciences and Applied Physics: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8523.2
Department of English: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8523.5
Department of the Fine Arts: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8528.3
Announcement of the Department of French: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8530.4
Courses in general education: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8532.2
Division of Geological Sciences: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8532.5
Department of Germanic Languages and Literatures: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8532.8
Division of History, Government, and Economics: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8538.2
Courses in the history of religions: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8538.6
Courses offered in the humanities: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8540.3
Department of Landscape Architecture: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8548.2
Department of Mathematics: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8553.2
Courses in medical sciences: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8554.2
Higher degrees in medical sciences: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8554.4
Department of Military Science: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8555.4
Division of mining and metallurgy: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8555.5
Department of Music: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8557.2
Courses offered in the natural sciences: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8558.3
Department of Naval Science and Tactics: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8558.6
Instruction in oceanography: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8564.4
Department of Philosophy: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8570.3
Division of Physical Sciences: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8570.5
Department of Physics: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8570.7
Department of Psychology: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8572.6
Regional studies: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8575.3
Department of Romance Languages and Literatures: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8577.5
Division of Semitic Languages and History: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8580.2
Department of Social Ethics: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8582.2
Department of Social Relations: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8582.4
Courses offered in the social sciences: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8582.6
Department of Sociology: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8582.8
Department of Zoology: Harvard University Archives call number HUC 8598.2
Series Descriptions and Folder Lists
- 1901-1902
  Summary
  Incomplete. Lacks No. 9. Department of French, 1901-1902, May 23, 1901; No. 32. Department of Germanic, 1901-1902, October 1, 1901; and No. 37. Annual reports, President and Treasurer, 1900-1901, January 25, 1902.
  - New Series, No. 1. Announcement of the summer courses for 1901, 1901 (HU 75.25 Box 1)
  - New Series, No. 2. Summer School of Arts and Sciences, 1901, March 20, 1901 (HU 75.25 Box 1)
  - New Series, No. 3. Summer School of Theology, third session, July 2-19, 1901, March 30, 1901 (HU 75.25 Box 1)
  - New Series, No. 4. Law School, 1901-1902, April 30, 1901 (HU 75.25 Box 1)
  - New Series, No. 5. The Divinity School, 1901-1902, April 30, 1901 (HU 75.25 Box 1)
  - New Series, No. 5, extra edition. The Divinity School, 1901-1902, second edition, April 30, 1901 (HU 75.25 Box 1)
  - New Series, No. 7. Department of the Classics and Department of Indo-Iranian Languages, 1901-1902, May 10, 1901 (HU 75.25 Box 1)
  - New Series, No. 8. Announcement of the courses of instruction provided by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences for the academic year 1901-1902, May 20, 1901 (HU 75.25 Box 1)
  - New Series, No. 8, extra edition. Announcement of the courses of instruction provided by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences for the academic year 1901-1902, second edition, June 25, 1901 (HU 75.25 Box 1)
  - New Series, No. 8, extra edition. Announcement of the courses of instruction provided by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences for the academic year 1901-1902, third edition, January 21, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 1)
  - New Series, No. 10. Division of Music, 1901-1902, May 27, 1901 (HU 75.25 Box 1)
  - New Series, No. 11. Division of Geology, comprising the Departments of Geology and Geography, Mineralogy and Petrography, and Mining and Metallurgy, 1901-1902, May 31, 1901 (HU 75.25 Box 1)
  - New Series, No. 12. Courses in education, 1901-1902, June 3, 1901 (HU 75.25 Box 1)
  - New Series, No. 13. Division of Philosophy, 1901-1902, June 7, 1901 (HU 75.25 Box 1)
  - New Series, No. 14. Medical School of Harvard University, announcement of courses for graduates, 1901-1902, June 12, 1901 (HU 75.25 Box 1)
  - New Series, No. 15. Division of Mathematics with the courses in astronomy, 1901-1902, June 18, 1901 (HU 75.25 Box 1)
  - New Series, No. 16. Division of History and Political Science comprising the Departments of History and Government and Economics, June 21, 1901 (HU 75.25 Box 1)
  - New Series, No. 17. Department of Zoology, 1901-1902, June 26, 1901 (HU 75.25 Box 1)
  - New Series, No. 18. Department of English, 1901-1902, July 1, 1901 (HU 75.25 Box 1)
  - New Series, No. 19. Division of Engineering, 1901-1902, July 5, 1901 (HU 75.25 Box 1)
  - New Series, No. 20. Division of Chemistry, 1901-1902, July 11, 1901 (HU 75.25 Box 1)
  - New Series, No. 22. Papers used at the examinations for admission to Harvard College and the Lawrence Scientific School, June 1901, July 24, 1901 (HU 75.25 Box 2)
  - New Series, No. 24. Opportunities for religious worship, instruction and fellowship, 1901-1902, August 3, 1901 (HU 75.25 Box 1)
  - New Series, No. 25. Rank list for 1900-1901, August 5, 1901 (HU 75.25 Box 1)
  - New Series, No. 26. Rules relating to College studies, 1901-1902, August 8, 1901 (HU 75.25 Box 1)
  - New Series, No. 27. Information for special students in Harvard College, 1901-1902, August 12, 1901 (HU 75.25 Box 1)
  - New Series, No. 28. The Medical School, 1901-1902, August 17, 1901 (HU 75.25 Box 1)
  - New Series, No. 28, extra edition. The Medical School, 1901-1902, second edition, November 15, 1901 (HU 75.25 Box 1)
  - New Series, No. 29. The Lawrence Scientific School, 1901-1902, August 27, 1901 (HU 75.25. Box 2)
  - New Series, No. 31. Division of American archaeology and ethnology, courses in anthropology, 1901-1902, September 7, 1901 (HU 75.25 Box 1)
  - New Series, No. 34. Information concerning the departments under the charge of the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, namely Harvard College, Lawrence Scientific School, the Graduate School, 1901-1902, November 30, 1901 (HU 75.25 Box 1)
  - New Series, No. 35. The Harvard University catalogue, 1901-1902, December 20, 1901 (HU 75.25 Box 2)
  - New Series, No. 38. The Summer School of Arts and Sciences, 1902, January 31, 1902 (HU 75.25. Box 3)
  - New Series, No. 39. Medical School of Harvard University, announcement of the summer courses for 1902, February 20, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - New Series, No. 40. Summer courses in physical education,1902, March 5, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - New Series, No. 41. Department of Mining and Metallurgy, 1901-1902, February 28, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 1)
- 1902-1903
  - 42. Announcement of the Divinity School, 1902-1903, March 29, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - 42, extra edition. Announcement of the Divinity School, 1902-1903, second edition, June 30, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - 43. Divinity School of Harvard University, Summer School of Theology, fourth session, July 1-18, 1902, April 7, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - 44. The Law School, 1902-1903, April 11, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 2)
  - 45. Lawrence Scientific School, announcement of programme in anatomy and physiology, 1901-1902, May 1, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - 46. Division of Music, 1902-1903, May 13, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - 47. Division of Geology, Departments of Geology and Geography and Mineralogy and Petrography, 1902-1903, May 17, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - 48. Department of French and other Romance Languages and Literatures, 1902-1903, May 20, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - 49. Division of Chemistry, 1902-1903, May 26, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - 50. Announcement of the courses of instruction, 1902-1903, May 28, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - 50, extra edition. Announcement of the courses of instruction, 1902-1903, second edition, July 1, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - 51. Department of the Classics and Department of Indic Philology, 1902-1903, June 2, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - 52. Medical School of Harvard University, announcement of courses for graduates, 1902-1903, June 6, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - 53. Division of Philosophy, 1902-1903, June 9, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - 54. Division of American archaeology and ethnology, courses in anthropology, 1902-1903, June 12, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - 55. Division of History and Political Science, comprising the Departments of History and Government and Economics, 1902-1903, June 14, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - 56. The Graduate School, 1902, June 21, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
    Catalogue of officers and students, 1901-1902, and announcements, 1902-1903
  - 57. Department of Germanic Languages and Literatures, 1902-1903, July 1, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - 58. Department of English, 1902-1903, July 5, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - 59. Division of Physics, 1902-1903, July 8, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - 60. Courses in education, 1902-1903, July 2, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - 61. Division of Mathematics, with the courses in astronomy, 1902-1903, July 10, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - 62. Division of Engineering, 1902-1903, July 12, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - 63. Lawrence Scientific School, announcement of the Department of Architecture, 1902-1903, August 1, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - 65. Rules relating to College studies, 1902-1903, August 7, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - 66. Papers used at the examinations for admission to Harvard College and the Lawrence Scientific School, June 1902, August 11, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - 67. Department of Zoology, 1902-1903, August 15, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - 68. The Lawrence Scientific School, 1902-1903, August 18, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - 70. Announcement of the Medical School, 1902-1903, first edition, September 2, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - 71. Department of Mining and Metallurgy, 1902-1903, September 2, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - 72. Opportunities provided for religious worship, instruction and fellowship, 1902-1903, August 29, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - 75. Information concerning the departments under the charge of the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1902-1903, December 26, 1902 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - 77. Annual reports of the President and the Treasurer of Harvard College, 1901-1902, January 31, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 2)
- 1903-1904
  - 78. The Summer School of Arts and Sciences, 1903, February 24, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 3)
  - 79. Medical School of Harvard University, announcement of the summer courses for 1903, February 28, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
  - 80. Divinity School, Summer School of Theology, fifth session, July 7-23, 1903, March 10, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
  - 81. The Graduate School, second edition, May 15, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
    Catalogue of officers and students, 1902-1903, and announcements, 1903-1904
  - 82. The Divinity School, 1903-1904, April 10, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
  - 83, extra edition. Announcement of the courses of instruction provided by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences for the academic year, 1903-1904, second edition, June 24, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
  - 84. Division of Anthropology, 1903-1904, April 18, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
  - 85. Department of Botany, 1903-1904, April 22, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
  - 86. Department of French and other Romance Languages and Literatures, 1903-1904, April 25, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
  - 87. Department of the Classics and Department of Indic Philology, 1903-1904, April 29, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
  - 88. Division of Physics, 1903-1904, May 1, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
  - 89. Division of Geology, Departments of Geology and Geography, and Mineralogy and Petrography, 1903-1904, May 5, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
  - 90. The Law School, 1903-1904, May 12, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
  - 91. Department of English, May 19, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
  - 92. Division of Philosophy, 1903-1904, May 23, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
  - 93. Courses in education, 1903-1904, May 28, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
  - 94. Division of History and Political Science, comprising the Departments of History and Government and Economics, 1903-1904, June 1, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
  - 95. Department of Germanic Languages and Literatures, 1903-1904, June 4, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
  - 96. Department of Zoology, 1903-1904, June 8, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
  - 97. Division of Semitic Languages and History, 1903-1904, June 11, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
  - 98. Department of Architecture, 1903-1904, June 15, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
  - 99. Division of Engineering, 1903-1904, June 22, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
  - 100. Department of Mining and Metallurgy, 1903-1904, July 1, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
  - 102. Division of Chemistry, 1903-1904, July 11, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
  - 103. Division of Mathematics, with the courses in astronomy, 1903-1904, July 13, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
  - 104. Faculty of Arts and Sciences, rank list for 1902-1903, July 25, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
  - 105. Rules relating to college studies, 1903-1904, July 31, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
  - 106. Medical School, announcement of courses for graduates, 1903-1904, August 1, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
  - 107. The Medical School, 1903-1904, first edition, August 22, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
  - 107, extra edition. The Medical School, 1903-1904, second edition, November 10, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
  - 108. Lawrence Scientific School, 1903-1904, September 1, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
  - 109. Opportunities provided for religious worship,instruction and fellowship, 1903-1904, September 2, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
  - 112. The Graduate School, 1903-1904, November 25, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 4)
  - 114. Information concerning the departments under the charge of the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1903-1904, December 28, 1903 (HU 75.25 Box 5)
- 1904-1905
  - 117. The Summer School of Arts and Sciences, 1904, February 20, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 118. Medical School, announcement of the summer courses for 1904, February 29, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 119. The Law School, 1904-1905, March 26, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 120. The Divinity School, Summer School of Theology, sixth session, July 5-21, 1904, March 30, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 121. The Divinity School, 1904-1905, April 6, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 122. Department of French and other Romance Languages and Literatures, 1904-1905, April 12, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 122, extra edition. Department of French and other Romance Languages and Literatures, 1904-1905, [second edition,] October 29, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 123. Division of Anthropology, 1904-1905, April 15, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 124. Department of the Classics and Department of Indic Philology, 1904-1905, April 18, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 125. Division of Music, 1904-1905, April 25, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 126. Division of Geology, Departments of Geology and Geography, and Mineralogy and Petrography, 1904-1905, April 29, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 127. Division of Chemistry, 1904-1905, May 6, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 128. Announcement of the courses of instruction provided by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences for the academic year 1904-1905, May 12, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 128, extra edition. Announcement of the courses of instruction provided by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences for the academic year 1904-1905, second edition, June 25, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 129. Division of History and Political Science, comprising the Departments of History and Government and Economics, 1904-1905, May 15, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 130. Courses of education, 1904-1905, May 20, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 131. Department of English, 1904-1905, May 24, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 132. Department of Botany, 1904-1905, May 28, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 133. Department of Germanic Languages and Literatures,1904-1905, June 4, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 134. Department of Mining and Metallurgy, 1904-1905, June 10, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 135. Division of Philosophy, 1904-1905, June 14, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 136. D ivision of Physics, 1904-1905, June 18, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 137. Division of Semitic Languages and History, 1904-1905, June 22, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 138. Division of Engineering, 1904-1905, June 29, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 139. Programme in Forestry, 1904-1905, July 5, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 140. Opportunities provided for religious worship, instruction, and fellowship, 1904-1905, July 9, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 141. Division of Mathematics, with the courses in astronomy, 1904-1905, July 12, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 142. Department of Zoology, 1904-1905, July 16, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 143. Department of Architecture, 1904-1905, July 23, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 144. Rules relating to college studies, 1904-1905, July 27, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 146. Medical School, courses for graduates, 1904-1905, August 10, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 148. The Lawrence Scientific School, 1904-1905, September 8, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
  - 149, extra edition. Medical School, 1904-1905, second edition, November 10, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 6)
- Volume II, issued December 1904-October 1905
  - 1. Harvard University catalogue, 1904-1905,December 21, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 7)
  - 2. Information concerning the departments under the charge of the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1904-1905, December 28, 1904 (HU 75.25 Box 9)
  - 4. Reports of the President and the Treasurer of Harvard College, 1903-1904, January 30, 1905 (HU 75.25 Box 5)
  - 5. Divinity School, Summer School of Theology, seventh session, subject: The Bible, July 5-21, 1905, February 10, 1905 (HU 75.25 Box 9)
  - 6. The Summer School of Arts and Sciences, 1905, February 28, 1905 (HU 75.25 Box 8)
  - 7. The Medical School, summer courses for 1905, March 27, 1905 (HU 75.25 Box 9)
  - 8. The Law School, 1905-1906, March 31, 1905 (HU 75.25 Box 8)
  - 9. The Divinity School, 1905-1906, April 12, 1905 (HU 75.25 Box 8)
  - 10. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1905-1906, April 15, 1905 (HU 75.25 Box 8)
  - 11. Division of Anthropology, 1905-1906, April 20, 1905 (HU 75.25 Box 8)
  - 12. Department of French and other Romance Languages and Literatures, 1905-1906, April 22, 1905 (HU 75.25 Box 8)
  - 13. Department of the Classics and Department of Indic Philology, 1905-1906, April 27, 1905 (HU 75.25 Box 8)
  - 14. Department of Germanic Languages and Literatures, 1905-1906, April 19, 1905 (HU 75.25 Box 8)